

Burhan Yudha Prawira UI/UX Designer

+6282322575527

burhanyudhaprawira@gmail.com dribbble.com/burhanyudha Wonogiri, Central Java, Indonesia

SUMMARY

Specializing in User Experience Design and User Interface Design for Apps and Website. Expert using Design Thinking method and understands building User Experience starting from research, creating user personas & customer journeys until making UI with the design system to combining empathy and beautiful design taste thus creating a perfect user experience that makes users seamless to use our products

EXPERIENCE

09/2020 - 01/2023 **UI/UX Designer**

Infinity UX Agency

finish UI Things in project Fluxys, Infrabel, Fujitsu

06/2020 - 09/2020 **Quality Assurance**

Travada Project

Helps ensure that the product meets all quality standards in each component

03/2020 - 05/2020 **UI Designer**

KataKerja Project

Help another member finish UI

02/2020 - 03/2020 **UI Designer**

GITSolution

Finish Belanja Keramik Mobile App

01/2018 - 08/2020 **UI/UX Designer**

Freelance

EDUCATION

2022 Bachelor of Informatics Engineering

Amikom University Yogyakarta Faculty of Computer Science

CERTIFICATES

03/2020 - Present Binar Academy Bootcamp - UI/UX 2 Months & QA 4 Months

05/2019 - Present Buildwithangga - Fullstack Web Developer

SKILLS

Web Design Expert Mobile Design Expert

Design Thinking Expert Prototypes Expert **Email Template** Advanced user-centered designs Expert wireframes User Persona Expert Expert **Competitive Analys** Expert mockups Expert **Usability Testing** Expert User Interface Expert **User Flows** Expert User Experience Expert

LANGUAGES

Indonesia Native English Intermediate